manycam.com 2015-09-21

# ManyCam Privacy Policy

## Introduction

Protecting personal information is a core ManyCam value. This privacy statement describes how we collect and use the personal information you provide on our website. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or delete it. 

ManyCam abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

## Information Collection

As is true of most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data. We also gather data from Google's Interest-based advertising and 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics. We use this information, which does not identify individual visitors, to analyze trends, to measure visitor usage and interest, to administer and improve the functionality of the website, to track visitors' movements around the site and to gather information about the geographic location of our visitors as a whole. We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") about our visitors at this website. No further information regarding our website visitors, other than the browser-level information described above, is collected at this website in any manner whatsoever or for any purpose. 

We may also gather information such as Windows OS version, primary monitor resolution, video preset count, and apps used with ManyCam. This information does not identify individual visitors by any means and is only used for the analysis of trends and to help improve our software. 

Unless a user has opted out by modifying his/her preferences, upon registration, we may use any e-mail address that we are provided with to notify users of the existence of new contents or promotions in areas concerning which they have expressed an interest. You may request that we stop sending you such notices, at any time thereafter, by following the instructions mentioned in our e-mails. 

ManyCam Pro users enter their email address, postal address, and billing data to purchase our software. This data (minus the billing data) is linked to the ManyCam Pro customer's private Pro serial/activation number and the customer's full name, email address, city, state, country, and postal code appears in the ManyCam Pro "About" window. ManyCam Pro user info is sometimes held on our servers and is encrypted. We never store or access any user credit card or any type of payment system billing data on our servers. ManyCam uses professional third party encrypted and secure billing services for billing transactions like Cleverbridge.com or Paypal.com. 

## Cookies

A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies. 

We use cookies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve the quality of our services. Our servers automatically record information when you visit our website, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. 

## Sharing of Information

ManyCam does not and will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies, except to provide products or services you have requested, with your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * From time to time, we may provide some of the personal information that we collected to trusted business partners that work on behalf of or with ManyCam under confidentiality agreements which cover our users’ personal information as well as guarantees that our partner provides the same level of protection to your information as our organization does. As the case may be, such business partners may use your personal information to help ManyCam communicate with you about our offers and those of our marketing partners. However, our business partners do not have any independent right to share or otherwise use your information; 
  * We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ManyCam’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; 

## Policy Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes in a conspicuous manner to this Privacy Policy, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

## Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
Visicom Media Inc  
6200 Taschereau  
Suite 304  
Brossard QC Canada  
J4W 3J8

Email:
